The unemployment
rate for
16 to 24
16 to
year olds- Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm, right has
olds- Mm-hmm.
moved to
12%. 12%,
big increase.
And what is
that saying?
That's saying that
That's saying
entry-level jobs
are not being
created the way
not being
they used
to be.
To those
people, I say,
people, I
you must have
in your mind
must have
an idea for
a new business,
new business,
something that frustrates
something that
you, an unmet
need. Well, now
need. Well,
you can go
to ChatGPT, you
can go to
can go
Grok, and you
can have an
can have
assistant help you
assistant help
build out that
business. Just
interview for jobs,
but also think
about new business
new business
ideas. I think
we're going to
we're going
see entrepreneurial
explosion here.
Well, and speaking
of entrepreneurial explosion,
entrepreneurial explosion,
I think about
how long you
think about
have certainly been
have certainly